What if the Vincents are not from America.
如果文森特人不是来自美国怎么办。
What if they're from England or some other country.
如果他们来自英国或其他国家怎么办。
Well then we have some other things to deal with.
那么我们还有一些其他的事情要处理。
So let's say that Mr. and Mrs. Vincent Lydia and David are from the UK and their phones do not work
因此，假设文森特·莉迪亚和大卫夫妇来自英国，他们的手机无法使用
in the United States.
在美国。
And I'm thinking about this because because of me I'm not me Luke.
我正在考虑这个，因为因为我，我不是我卢克。
Sorry Luke is thinking about this because he's a very thoughtful person.
抱歉，卢克正在考虑这个问题，因为他是一个非常有思想的人。
So he asks them or needs to talk about whether or not they need to get SIM cards in the airport one
所以他问他们或需要谈谈他们是否需要在机场拿到 SIM 卡一张
good place to get a SIM card is the airport.
获得 SIM 卡的好地方是机场。
You don't have to if you need to get a SIM card you might go to maybe a shop in the downtown area that
如果您需要一张 SIM 卡，您不必这样做，您可能会去市中心的一家商店
might be OK too.
也可能没问题。
Maybe it's cheaper there but let's just look at how we can describe that if we need to.
也许那里更便宜，但让我们看看如果需要，我们如何描述它。
How can we ask Mr. and Mrs. Vincent about this.
我们怎么能问文森特先生和夫人呢。
So here are the questions.
所以这里有问题。
Do you have phone coverage here.
你这里有电话覆盖吗？
Coverage is what we use when we talk about whether or not we're able to get a signal and it doesn't
当我们谈论我们是否能够获得信号而它不能时，我们使用覆盖率
have to be going to another country.
必须要去另一个国家。
It could mean for example that there's no signal where we are now even if we're in our own our own country.
例如，这可能意味着即使我们在我们自己的国家，也没有迹象表明我们现在所处的位置。
Maybe because we are out of range or underground we're in the desert whatever.
也许是因为我们不在范围内或在地下，所以我们在沙漠中。
There's no coverage here there's no coverage.
这里没有报道，没有报道。
Maybe in the desert I can't get a signal underground.
也许在沙漠中我无法在地下获得信号。
So anyway we can say it in this case.
所以无论如何我们可以在这种情况下说出来。
Do you have phone coverage here.
你这里有电话覆盖吗？
Here means maybe if they're from another country this means in the U.S. A because they're in New York.
这里的意思是如果他们来自另一个国家，这意味着在美国，因为他们在纽约。
Or do you need a local SIM card.
或者您需要本地 SIM 卡。
While we're still at the airport this suggests still at the airport that this is a good place to get
虽然我们仍在机场，但这表明仍在机场，这是一个很好的去处
it.
它。
It's a good place to get it.
这是一个获得它的好地方。
We're still here means we're going to leave soon.
我们还在这里意味着我们很快就要离开了。
We're still here.
我们还在这里。
That means we're about to go.
这意味着我们要走了。
Does your SIM card work in the States.
你的 SIM 卡在美国能用吗？
Sometimes we call America just the states the USA.
有时我们称美国只是美国。
We just say the states the United States of America.
我们只说美利坚合众国。
Does your SIM card work in the States.
你的 SIM 卡在美国能用吗？
Does it function.
有没有作用。
Does it function in the States.
它是否在美国发挥作用。
OK so this is a common question that we will ask in this sort of situation.
好的，这是我们在这种情况下会问的一个常见问题。
Or if you have maybe a friend who is a guest in your country and maybe they're staying at your home
或者如果你有一个朋友在你的国家做客，他们可能住在你家
whatever similar situations you might need to help them and you'll ask this question.
无论您可能需要帮助他们的任何类似情况，您都会问这个问题。
These three are quite common and you can ask variations of these as well.
这三个很常见，您也可以询问这些变体。
Now this might come after we've started walking to the car.
现在这可能会在我们开始步行到汽车后发生。
So just want to mention by the way if it's time to do that right we've done the introductions.
所以顺便提一下，如果是时候做这件事，我们已经做了介绍。
We've talked about how the flight was.
我们已经讨论了飞行的情况。
We've said the plan.
我们已经说了计划。
Well then we're going to say all right all right well well I've I've got the car parked outside.
那么我们会说好吧好吧好吧好吧我已经把车停在外面了。
Shall we.
我们可以。
That means shall we go now.
这意味着我们现在就走吧。
It's a very common question when you want to recommend what we do.
当您想推荐我们的工作时，这是一个非常常见的问题。
Well I've got the car parked outside.
嗯，我已经把车停在外面了。
Shall we.
我们可以。
Or are.
或者是。
Are you ready to head head out now head out just means go.
你准备好出发了吗？现在出发就意味着出发。
So we could just say that or we could add to the the car.
所以我们可以这么说，或者我们可以添加到汽车中。
You ready to head out to the car.
你准备出门上车。
Or or when we could say shall we.
或者当我们可以说我们应该。
Shall we go.
我们走吧。
I'll take that.
我会接受的。
I'll take that Lydia.
我会带走那个莉迪亚。
Take what.
拿什么。
Her bag.
她的背包。
She's carrying a bag.
她背着一个包。
It's very polite.
这是非常有礼貌的。
If you pick someone up at the airport to take especially if it's a lady to take a lady's back.
如果你在机场接人带特别是如果是一个女士带一个女士的背。
Very polite.
彬彬有礼的。
I'll take that video.
我会拍那个视频的。
Or can I take that for you if you want to ask it.
或者，如果你想问的话，我可以替你拿走。
Can I take that for you Lydia.
我可以为你拿那个吗，莉迪亚。
She might say oh no that's OK I've got it I've got it.
她可能会说哦，不，没关系，我知道了，我知道了。
Ah it's no trouble It's no trouble.
啊，没问题，没问题。
That's OK.
没关系。
Thanks anyway.
不管怎么说，还是要谢谢你。
If you want to refuse someone politely thanks anyway thanks anyway.
如果你想礼貌地拒绝某人，无论如何谢谢。
I'm OK.
我可以。
Finally we could say please follow me.
最后我们可以说请跟我来。
We can go out to the car.
我们可以出去坐车。
Please follow me please follow me.
请关注我请关注我。
Or sometimes after me please.
或者有时请在我之后。
After me please.
请在我之后。
Or if you want to be very informal.
或者，如果您想非常随意。
Well let's go let's go.
好吧，我们走吧。
Although that is pretty informal usually we use let's go with friends.
虽然这很不正式，但我们通常使用“让我们和朋友一起去”。
Ready.
准备好。
Yeah.
是的。
Let's go let's go.
走吧，走吧。
So anyway we are walking along in the airport and I've asked the question do you need a local SIM card
所以不管怎样，我们在机场散步，我问过你需要一张当地的 SIM 卡吗
while we're still at the airport and one of them answers.
当我们还在机场时，其中一个回答了。
Maybe it's Lydia.
也许是莉迪亚。
Actually I think we will need to get at least one and then she might turn to her husband and say Right
实际上，我认为我们至少需要得到一个，然后她可能会转向她的丈夫并说对
David.
大卫。
Or maybe he says actually I think we will need one or maybe two.
或者也许他说实际上我认为我们需要一两个。
Do you need one.
你需要一个吗。
Maybe they need to talk with each other as well.
也许他们也需要互相交谈。
OK.
好的。
But I think we will need at least one means.
但我认为我们至少需要一种方法。
Yes.
是的。
Let's stop and buy one here at the airport.
让我们在机场停下来买一个。
We're okay actually means they don't need one.
我们很好实际上意味着他们不需要一个。
We're okay.
我们没事。
Actually our plan works abroad.
实际上我们的计划在国外有效。
What does plan mean.
计划是什么意思。
Well your plan refers to what you have in your home country either for internet or your phone.
好吧，您的计划是指您在本国拥有的互联网或手机。
It's often called a calling plan or sometimes it's called a data plan or sometimes it's called a service
它通常称为呼叫计划，有时称为数据计划，有时称为服务
plan.
计划。
The company that provides your service is sometimes called a service provider.
为您提供服务的公司有时称为服务提供商。
Sometimes in America for example T-Mobile.
有时在美国，例如 T-Mobile。
AT&amp;T.
美国电话电报公司
These companies are also called carriers carriers cell phone carriers.
这些公司也被称为运营商运营商手机运营商。
Anyway we're okay actually.
反正我们其实还好。
This is a way to say no.
这是一种拒绝的方式。
Would you like some chocolate.
你想要一些巧克力吗？
I'm OK actually.
其实我没事。
Would you like a piece of pizza.
你想要一块比萨饼吗？
I'm okay actually.
我其实没事。
Do you need me to help you with that bag.
你需要我帮你拿那个包吗？
I'm okay actually it's a great way to say no very politely.
我很好，实际上这是非常礼貌地说不的好方法。
We can also say I'm good but that's less formal.
我们也可以说我很好，但这不那么正式。
We can say I'm fine.
我们可以说我很好。
Actually it means no.
其实就是没有的意思。
It's very very nice way to say no.
这是非常非常好的拒绝方式。
And it's really easy.
这真的很容易。
OK.
好的。
Our plan is what we pay for each month to our carrier maybe maybe for our phone abroad works abroad
我们的计划是我们每月向运营商支付的费用，也许是我们在国外的电话在国外工作的费用
abroad.
国外。
Just means in other countries not your own country not your local country not just domestically domestically.
只是指在其他国家，不是你自己的国家，不是你当地的国家，不仅仅是在国内。
Just means in your own country.
只是意味着在你自己的国家。
Domestically we may also need to maybe ask a question about exchanging currency exchanging money exchanging
在国内，我们可能还需要问一个关于兑换货币兑换货币的问题交换
cash if they haven't done that before.
如果他们以前没有这样做过现金。
Before they left.
在他们离开之前。
If they haven't exchanged their money into for example U.S. dollars then they may need to do it on arrival
如果他们没有将钱兑换成美元，那么他们可能需要在抵达时进行兑换
to ask that Luke will say Do you need to exchange any cash or money or currency while we're here again.
问卢克会说我们再次在这里时，您需要兑换任何现金或金钱或货币吗？
Same question while we're in the airport it's a good idea to do it before you get out of the airport.
同样的问题，当我们在机场时，最好在您离开机场之前完成。
That's a travel tip.
这是一个旅行小贴士。
Actually yes I'd like to says maybe David.
实际上是的，我想说也许大卫。
Yes I'd like to.
是的，我愿意。
Again if they've already done it David might say no.
如果他们已经这样做了，大卫可能会再次拒绝。
We already have some local money or we've already done it or we did it before we left.
我们已经有一些当地的钱，或者我们已经完成了，或者我们在离开之前已经完成了。
Maybe they're very responsible.
也许他们很负责任。
Prepare well.
好好准备。
Actually yes I'd like to.
实际上是的，我愿意。
Would you recommend using an A.T.M. or going to an exchange counter.
你会推荐使用 A.T.M.或者去兑换柜台。
So sometimes you can get cash using a credit card even if it's not in your country.
因此，有时即使不在您所在的国家/地区，您也可以使用信用卡获取现金。
Go to the A.T.M. put it in credit card and you get local currency it takes it out of your own maybe
去 A.T.M.把它放在信用卡里，你会得到当地货币，它可能会从你自己身上取出
credit from from your own currency.
来自您自己的货币的信用。
Maybe there's a fee.
也许是要收费的。
That's what I usually do.
这就是我通常做的。
By the way cause I'm a little bit lazy about that kind of thing.
顺便说一句，因为我对那种事情有点懒惰。
OK so would you recommend using an A.T.M. or going to an exchange counter.
好的，你会推荐使用 A.T.M.或者去兑换柜台。
This is the one that you usually find in the airport.
这是您通常在机场找到的那个。
Now it's probably better to do exchanging in the airport because you don't usually find exchange counters
现在最好在机场进行兑换，因为您通常找不到兑换柜台
around around the city.
在城市周围。
Sometimes depending on where you are but the airport is a good location for it.
有时取决于你在哪里，但机场是一个很好的位置。
OK now what should we recommend.
好的，现在我们应该推荐什么。
Well we could say I would recommend or my suggestion is we could say.
好吧，我们可以说我会推荐或者我的建议是我们可以说。
My suggestion is or would be to just use the A.T.M. it's very convenient.
我的建议是或将只是使用 A.T.M.这很方便。
Just use your credit card or hide.
只需使用您的信用卡或隐藏。
I would recommend going to an exchange counter because it's just over there.
我建议去兑换柜台，因为它就在那边。
It's just over there.
它就在那边。
Or there's one right over there.
或者那里有一个。
Sometimes we say right over there if it's nearby right over there.
有时我们会说就在那边，如果它就在那边附近。
The exchange rate is pretty good.
汇率还不错。
Exchange rate means the amount of local currency you get from your own currency means money.
汇率是指您从自己的货币中获得的当地货币数量，即货币。
Right.
正确的。
The local currency you get and the exchange rate goes up and down.
您获得的当地货币和汇率会上下波动。
If we say it's a good exchange rate that means you get more money from your money.
如果我们说这是一个很好的汇率，这意味着你可以从你的钱中得到更多的钱。
Basically if it's a bad exchange rate then kind of lose money.
基本上，如果这是一个糟糕的汇率，那么有点赔钱。
And also we could talk about fees the exchange rate is nothing about what you pay to the people at the
而且我们还可以谈论费用，汇率与您向人们支付的费用无关
counter.
柜台。
The exchange rate is just the value of your money compared to the value of the money you're getting.
汇率只是你的钱与你得到的钱的价值相比的价值。
The fee is what you pay extra.
费用是您额外支付的费用。
So I could say if I want to talk about fees the exchange rate is pretty good right now and maybe the
所以我可以说，如果我想谈谈费用，现在的汇率还不错，也许
fees the fees they're over there at that counter are low.
费用他们在那个柜台那里的费用很低。
The fees are low that means they don't charge very much.
费用很低，这意味着他们不会收取太多费用。
Okay thanks.
好的谢谢。
That means he has.
这意味着他有。
David has accepted my recommendation.
大卫接受了我的推荐。
So this is something that comes up sometimes not as often maybe as the phone situation but whenever
因此，有时会出现这种情况，可能不像电话情况那样经常出现，但无论何时
you need to help somebody who's come to your country.
你需要帮助来到你国家的人。
This is how you would express basically whether or not they need to get local money.
这就是您基本上表达他们是否需要获得当地资金的方式。